wetoku.com 2010-11-21

# Wetoku :: Privacy Policy

## Personal Information

Your Wetoku Account. For some activities on Wetoku, like creating meetings, recording meetings, or deleting recordings you need a Wetoku Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 

Usage Information. When you use Wetoku, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the IP addresses of the people who attend your meetings, when you create and record meetings, when your videos are played back, the videos you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in Wetoku (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your Wetoku Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a tag (also called a "web beacon") in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery. 

Content Uploaded to Site. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others. 

## Uses

If you submit personal information to Wetoku, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of Wetoku, and to process any flagging activity or other communication you send to us. 

We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Wetoku changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use cookies, web beacons, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Wetoku; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

## Information That is Publicly Available

When you create a Wetoku Account, some information about your Wetoku Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of Wetoku. This may include the date you opened your Wetoku Account, the date you last logged into your Wetoku Account, the number of videos you have recorded and the number of people who have viewed your videos. 

Any videos that you submit to Wetoku may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other Wetoku users or the general public. 

## Your Choices

If you have a Wetoku Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your “My Account” page. 

You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through Wetoku, in which case you can still view Wetoku videos embedded on other sites, but Wetoku may not be able to provide certain services to you. 

## Advertising on Wetoku

Wetoku may provide you with advertising, which we would strive to ensure is relevant and useful to you, and we may use cookies as well as other third party ad serving systems to do so. We may use a range of information including cookies, web beacons, IP addresses, usage data and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as browser type and operating system) to provide you with relevant advertising. 

Other third-party ad serving companies may display ads on Wetoku, provided they comply with our ad serving requirements. Wetoku does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Wetoku's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Wetoku is maintained and dealt with by Wetoku in accordance with this privacy policy. 

## More Information

Wetoku adheres to the US Safe Harbor privacy principles. For more information about the Safe Harbor framework or our registration, see the Department of Commerce's web site. 

For more information about our privacy practices, write to us at: 

Wetoku Privacy  
Wetoku, Inc.  
#101 DNS Bldg, 398-14 Seogyo-dong, Mapo-gu,  
Seoul, Republic of Korea 121-840
